you put on a cap, I just don’t understand.
вы одели пилотку вот просто не понимаю
You didn’t
Вы же не
wear it all your life for your grandfathers. It was the
одели всю жизнь за своих дедов Это был
Soviet Union, your grandfathers whom you
Советский Союз ваши деды которых вы
poured green paint on. Why When they stood
зелёнкой обливали Зачем Когда они вот
like that
так
Good afternoon, good day Yes, what do you
стояли Добрый день добрый Да а что у вас
write down about the coronavirus? Yes, this is what you have,
коронавирус записываете да вот это у вас
yes
да
I write it down No  I put on a mask so that I
записываю Нет я маску одела чтобы лица
don’t want my face to be Okay,
не хочу чтобы лицо было О'кей хорошо
okay, look, somehow you have Echo speakers,
да смотрите у вас как-то динамики Эхо
you can set it up differently so that there’s no Echo,
можете по-другому поставить чтоб Эхо не
but Echo How can I turn on the headphones or something?
было а Эхо А как мне наушники что ли
let's talk to the headphones,
включить да давайте наушники поговорим с
but I lost it, I say the earphone, the speaker, I
вот потеряла говорю наушник колонку
brought it now, I've brought ours Let's
принесла сейчас я наш науш Давайте да
try now, well, I can already see that you are an
сейчас попробую ну что я уже вижу что вы
interesting character, it’s interesting
интересный персонаж с вами интересно
to talk to you and you
поговорить а
’re recording Why and I’m collecting different
записываете Зачем а я собираю разные
opinions of people from Russia Well, I
мнения людей из России Ну у меня у меня
won’t have it  no such opinion so that you
не будет никакого такого мнения чтобы вы
will be happy about this M not so I look I’m
обрадовались этому М не так Я смотрите Я
not in order to rejoice or
ж не для того чтобы порадоваться или
annoy I collect you know as a
позлить я вот собираю знаете как
researcher I collect different things So you’re
исследователь я собираю разные лю Вот вы
asking people from Russia How do you
э спрашиваю у людей из России Как вы
feel about the war  in
относитесь к войне в
Ukraine this is a special operation Well, that’s what
Украине это спецоперация Ну у вас это
you call it, yes How do you feel about
называется так да Как вы относитесь к
it, I basically feel about it
этому я в принципе отношусь
Well, how can I say how I feel about it,
Ну как сказать как я отношусь
say I feel
скажи я отношусь из-за того я переживали
about it because I was worried about it because all the people are dying, both
отношусь потому что все люди погибают и
ours and
наши и
yours, but I want to say that I  after all, for
ваши но хочу сказать что я всё-таки за
my president and I think that he is right,
своего президента и я считаю что он прав
so Justify why he is right, that’s
у так Обоснуйте почему он прав вот
why it was necessary because he
почему это надо было потому что он за
worries about us and he did what he
нас переживает и он сделал так как
thought was necessary and we have millions, he has the
считал нужным а мы миллионы на нём
responsibility, all the responsibility,
ответственность вся вся ответственность
he understands  And look, and for him to
на нём понял А смотрите И для него такое
make such a decision was also such a big
решение принять было это тоже большой
one. Well, it seems to me that he took a long time, he was
такой Ну мне кажется он ну он долго он
probably eight years old. Yes, he
наверное восемь сколько летто Да
made this decision. Well, he made it.
принимал это решение Ну вот принял А вам
Don’t you think that in 1939,
не кажется что в тридцать девятом году
somewhere in Germany, there was also some  the girl
где-то в Германии тоже какая-то девушка
could say exactly the same thing, I trust
могла точно так же говорит я доверяю
my Adolf gi there, she could, yes. That
своему там адольфу ги могла могла да То
is, you just trust But you
есть вы получается просто доверяете Но
can’t even understand why this is being done,
даже не можете понять для чего делается
yes no, I understand because, well,
это да нет я понимаю потому что ну
because what kind of weapons were coming to
потому что вооружение какое это шло на
our side We are doing this too  knew We are
нашу сторону Мы же тоже это знали Мы
also ordinary
тоже простые
people  everyone was approaching America all
люди к нам приближались все Америка
the time why did she supply you with weapons all
постоянно почему она вас оружием всё
the time Yeah why and why well
время снабжал Угу зачем а зачем хорошо
look America now Finland
смотрите Америка вот сейчас Финляндия
will join NATO no Can I ask a question now
вступит в НАТО нет Можно я теперь вопрос
let’s ask you a question
задам давайте давайте вы вопрос задаёте
Let’s Zelensky is good for you
Давайте Зеленский у вас
Well what do people say about look
хороший Ну как люди про говорят смотрите
No I’m from you  I want to get an answer I’m
Нет я от вас хочу ответ получить Я же
answering you: Shut up, don’t
вам отвечаю Помолчите не людей не
irritate people, look at completely different
нервируй смотрите абсолютно разные
opinions, for example, I don’t consider him, for
мнения так например я не считаю его
example, a super president to be so
например супер президентом так
effective, but for example, now during the
эффективным но например сейчас во время
war he shows very good
войны он показывает очень хороший
actions. What actions to protect our
действия Какие действия по защите нашего
state, tell me  what actions
государства ну расскажите какие действия
do you look at in the international arena, that is,
смотрите на международной арене то есть
your president is an outcast, so And our president
ваш президент изгой так А наш президент
is now number one Well, who is number one?
сейчас номер один Ну кто кто номер один
Vladimir Zelensky,
Владимир Зеленский
yes, that is, look, you know
да то есть смотрите знаете В чём
Why for some reason Putin is number one, look
почему-то Путин номер один смотрите В
What is the essence of this war Zelensky was a
чём суть этой войны Зеленский был
clown and became the top  I still remained a clown
клоуном а стал топ я остался клоуном ещ
and But this old man of yours, what’s his name
и А вот этот ваш этот старичок как его
Putin Yes Vladimir Well, I must say that
Путин Да Владимир Ну надо говорить что
you forgot what his name is a clown,
вы забыли как его зовут клоуном
that’s what his name is, he
вот как его как его зовут он клоуном
became a clown, so why  can you explain
стал пут так ради чего можете обяснить
why your Soldiers are dying in Ukraine
ради чего ваши Солдаты умирают в Украине
for the sake of what we can’t say I’m
ради чего вот мы это не можем сказать Я
sitting here I can prove this to you or something
вот сижу Я это могу вам доказать что ли
you tell us why yours are dying with
Вы расскажите ради чего ваши погибают со
signs on their hands with these fascist ones,
знаками на руке вот с этими фашистскими
look ours are dying for
наши смотрите наши погибают за то чтобы
Boshe so that  you left here from Ukraine there is no
Боше чтоб вы отсюда ушли из Украины нет
reason to ask then you start
рели ме спрашивать потом вы начинаете
talking ugly I’m not talking about yours
некрасиво говорить Я же про ваших не
you just said so that more of
говорю вы сейчас сказали чтобы больше
yours is correct I didn’t just say so
ваших правильно Я же сейчас не сказала
that yours Wait
чтобы ваши Подожди
wait stop but I don’t  I feel sorry for the Russians in
подожди стоп а мне не жалко русских в
Ukraine Because they are occupiers Why
Украине Потому что они оккупанты Поче
because they are about And what
потому что они о А мальчишки вам что
did the boys do to you And you You felt sorry for the German
сделали А вам Вам жалко было немецких
soldiers who came here to our Lands there was
солдат которые пришли сюда на наши Земли
once a
когда-то
civil war There, not everyone was
ражда Там не все были
bad, but they came here with weapons
плохи но они с оружием пришли
Well, they are theirs  they said to go, not everyone
сюда Ну их же им сказали идти не все же
went of their own free will. Wait. That is, it
шли своей волей Подождите То есть
turns out. And so Putin is forcing
получается А так Путин загоняет насильно
soldiers into Ukraine, it turns out, Lord,
солдат в Украину получается Господи
you know now, if I start now, you
знаете сейчас я если начну вы сейчас на
’ll be too strong, now you’ll say again
сильно-то будете вы сейчас опять
2 good It is necessary that how many of yours
2 хорошо Надо чтобы а ваших сколько
have rotted, well, look at our Great Dane Neva,
сгнило ну смотрите наши уже дог Нева
how many of your Dogs are gone, you don’t
сколько ваших дог нело вам своих не
feel sorry for yours because your occupiers, you
жалко потому что ваши оккупанты вот вы
yourself are from which region of Russia, from which
сами с какой области России из какого
region, it doesn’t matter Well, it doesn’t matter,
региона неважно Ну как неважно вот
look, I’m from the city hme Well Tver Tver o
смотри я из города хме Ну Тверь Тверь о
Tver, you don’t know this,
Тверь это знать не знаете
yes, you have such a gangster, it’s you, and you are
да Бандитский такой у вас это вы а вы
some kind of distant journalist,
кто типа журналист далёкий какой-то да
some kind of one, a small, small programmer,
какой-то такой Мелкий мелкий програмист
yes, but you see, you’re not a small one  a big nurse
Да А вы вижу мелкая не крупная медсестра
like that No, I’m not a nurse and I’m not a big one,
такая Нет я не медсестра и не крупная
you know, that means a mask against Covid. A
знаете ыч значит маска от ковида
Soviet cap and blouse, this style of
Советская пилотка и кофточка такой стиль
combo is called Yes, look, what did
комбо называется Да так вот смотрите Что
you say? It seems to me that you’re not even a
к чему вы сказали мне кажется вы даже не
small-time
мелкий
journalist, an even smaller blouse,
журналист ещ мельче кофточка
I’m researching mental disorders of
я исследую психические отклонения
the Russians in the
Россиян на
background  geopolitics of the day Oh, Lord, you have your
фоне геополитики дне Ой Господи вы своих
deviations Count me, here I am calling, I
отклонений Посчитайте вот я звоню вот я
told you something bad when
вам что-нибудь сказала плохого когда
I called Well, I dialed That’s it, it connected with you
позвонила Ну набрала Вот это да с вами
And yours connects with me  they
соединилась А ваши соединяется со мной
immediately start yelling and I think
сразу начинают орать и у Мне кажется у
they have a
них
deviation to
отклонение
honestly show they think I’ve
честно показывать они думают
never seen them, well, maybe I haven’t
не видела их никогда ну их может и не
seen them, but I haven’t seen any damn
видела но какой-нибудь не видела блин
thing I haven’t seen Well, they all show they
что не видела Ну показывают все они
may be thinking I’ve never seen them Well, I
может думают Я никогда не видела Вот я
don’t know that  I need to look at your deviations
не знаю это у ваших отклонений надо
If I’m Russian Yesterday I
посмотреть Если я русская Я вчера причём
was sitting without this hat And why is this a hat
сидела без этой шапки А по это это шапка
about some kind or that I don’t don’t see it,
про какая-то или что я не не не вижу её
you can show me closely 40 years old they
можете близко показать мне 40 лет меня в
won’t take me in anymore Why is it
уже не возьмут А почему
too late they tried it before
всё уж поздно пробовали раньше не
tried it before  Now let's start And
пробовал раньше А сейчас начинать А
what kind of person do you
каким кем вы
work for? I don't work. My husband
работаете Я не работаю меня муж
provided for me. Yeah, and who
обеспечил Угу а муж кем
does my husband work for? Yes, my husband drives a big car. He
работае муж Да муж на машине на большой
works fighting in Ukraine, but in
Работает воюет в Украине правда ни в
no case. No way, no matter what kind of
коем случае Ни в коем слу на какой он
big car he works in, then, well,
большой машине работает тогда ну на фуре
he drives a truck.  works on a truck, and that is, and I understand,
Он работает на фуре а то есть а я понял
that is, that’s why no, he doesn’t go
то есть Вот почему нет он не ездит
there, he doesn’t go anywhere, No, he doesn’t work,
никуда туда не ездит Нет не работает
Ukraine is not at war, thank God, it doesn’t get under way, it’s
Украине не воюет слава Богу не трогается
hard in any way, it’s very hard, honestly,
у нас никак тяжело это очень тяжело чест
maybe  maybe he will be sent to defend the
скаж Может может его отправят защищать
Nazis’ Ukraine What if Ukraine attacks
фашистов А вдруг Украина нападёт на
Russia
Россию
Well, so what, I’m a man and who should
А ну и что мня мужен а кто тог должен
uraevo
ураево
so who I said that I’m against
того чтобы кто я же сказала что я против
stop you About someone dying but
стоп вы Про того чтобы кто-то умирал но
support the president’s decision on
поддерживайте решение президента по вот
this special operation Yes  yes yes, from which
этой спецоперации Да да да от которой
Everyone dies, that is, as a result of a
Все умирают то есть в результате
special operation, a huge number of people die,
спецоперации умирают люди огромное
you support it But you are
количество вы это поддерживаете Но вы
against someone dying, which
против того чтобы кто-то умирал что у
take it off from you Pilot Well, in short, if anything
вас снимите Пилот Ну короче если что
if anything I  I’ll make a dugout for my husband and hide
если что я мужу землянку выю и спрячу
him there,
его туда
I get it, I get it, I get it, in your
я понял понятно я понял понял у вас в
forest, I’ve already seen where the worst place is
лесу я уже увидела где место самое
if they’re bombing. I just recently
страшное если когда бомбят Я вот недавно
thought they were bombing you there. Yes, I say,
тут думала у вас там бомбят Да я говорю
Lord, this is where to run. Stay where you are, you’ll hit, you
Господи это вот куда бежать Стой на
won’t get hit.  God
месте попадёт не попадёт не дай Бог вот
forbid, God forbid, but Where can you run away? Just run to
не дай Бог а Куда убежишь просто Бежать
where sara ra Why Why did they put this cap
куда са ра Зачем Зачем эту пилотку одели
on themselves? Because this cap is actually
на себя Потому что это пилотка вообще
about our grandfathers. May 9th was and that’s why
это про наших дедов 9 мая было и поэтому
I have  cap I just put on you don’t
у меня пилотка Я просто одела ты не
know what May 9th is, I’ll even
знаешь что такое 9 мая я даже на ты
tell you now I’m always on you I’m looking
сейчас скажу я всегда на Вы я смотрю
why why is it May 9th why did you wear
почему зачем такое 9 мая зачем вы одели
a cap I just don’t understand You won’t
пилотку вот просто не понимаю Вы же не
wear your whole life for your grandfathers It was the
одеку всю жизнь за своих дедов Это был
Soviet Union yours  grandfathers whose grandfathers you
Советский Союз ваши деды которых вы
doused with greenery Why When they
зелёнкой обливали Зачем Когда они вот
stood like that wait wait now I so
так стояли подождите подождите сейчас я
that I don’t laugh about Let’s do it again
чтобы я не ржал о Давайте ещё раз А
Why are you laughing at oh damn you just
почему вы смеётесь над э блин вы просто
pile on so clearly I just
навалите так чётко Я просто не
can’t
могу
Let’s A  why is it funny on you like this? It
Давайте А почему вот так вот на вам
’s true, it’s not real, see
смешно Это правда не это реально сме 9
May 9th, it’s funny, it’s not funny, it’s not May 9th, it’s funny, you
мая смешно не смешно не 9 мая смешно вы
and your cap. How do you pile on?
с пилоткой Как вы навалите
Yes, just look, my grandfather fought
Да просто вот смотрите у меня дед воевал
like that too. Well, tell me now, I’m
тоже так Ну Ну вот расскажи сечас твое я
not wearing a cap today.  what ST or
не сижу в пилотке сегодня како СТ или
just to annoy you all I
просто вас всех позлить Я вчера
called yesterday they called me 300 times they put my glasses
позвонила меня 300 раз назвали меня очки
in 300 times you don’t make me angry you make
засунули 300 раз мои вы Не злите я проте
me laugh don’t make me angry
меня смешите Не злите
but
а а у
you have  I’m not
васу я не
angry, I’m not angry, I’m not angry, they’re just
злая я не зла я не злюсь они меня прям
trying to do this to me. And today I
вот это пытаются пытаются А я сегодня
decided to put a cap on them, just to
решила им пилотку одеть пря вот долить
top them off, why do you go out to the
их добить а зачем зачем вы выходите в
Ukrainian roulette to
украинскую там рулетку
talk? I want to see how the people
поговорить Я хочу посмотреть как народ
treat me in general, like the people are, well, crazy
относится вообще как народ вот ну
in
сумасшедшим в
caps they were the first to laugh Yes and in a
пилотках о первые засмеялись Да и в
sweater Don’t forget in a sweater Yes usually
кофте Не забудьте и в кофте Да обычно
everyone is without a jacket in caps And I’m in a sweater Yes
все без кофты в пилотках А я в кофте Да
and the nurse is wearing a mask
и в маске медсестра
No, I want to see and very angry
капец Нет я хочу посмотреть и очень злые
very aggressive very character Yes, I was
очень агрессивные очень персонаж Да я я
thinking with you about I’m not a character I’m a human being,
думал с вами про я не персонаж Я человек
40 years old and I have a daughter, a child, a husband, a daughter,
м 40 лет и у меня есть дочь ребёнок муж
a child and a husband
есть дочь ребёнок и муж
Yes, that’s enough
Да ну хватит
I’m a child, a husband yes But look, it
Я ребёнок муж да А вот смотрите
turns out I  I just wanted to sing with you about
получается Я просто хотел с вами на
serious topics, but I see that you
серьёзные темы поть но смотрю что Вы
are a comedic person, I’m not a
такое комедийный как бы человек со я не
comedic person, I can be serious,
комедийный человек я могу на серьёз те
you’re so straight forward, I think you’re a
настолько вы пря улы Мне кажется вы
comedic person, look at you, look at
комедийный вот смотрите на вас смотришь
me  I just look at you and laugh about
Я просто на вас смот и поржать о
you, where is your wife and where is your wife, where is your wife
а вас где жена а где жена у вас где жена
not on a truck? Like you,
не на фуре Как у вас типа
yes, I have a husband, well, you have a husband on Fury. And by
да у меня муж ну так у вас муж на Фури А
the way, my wife’s wife is sitting at my husband’s house,
кстати жена-то жена-то у моего мужа дома
married  The husband is at home, and where you are at
сидит женатого Мужа дома а у вас где на
work, he is plowing and plowing, and where you are, the wife is
работе подик да пашет а у вас где Жена
at work, and she is plowing at
на работе паве летке а она пашат на
work, yes, this is how it is done in Ukraine.
работе да у нас у нас так в Украине
But
принято А вот
look, after all, I want to. Let’s
смотрите всё ж таки я вот хочу Давайте
try some serious ones.  topics
раз всё-таки попробуем серьёзные темы
if Well, come on, you are against
если Ну давайте вы против того чтобы
people dying, but you support the
люди погибали но вы поддерживаете
actions of your president to carry out
действия вашего президента по проведению
this so-called special operation from
этой так называемой спецоперации от
which a lot of people die, including
которой погибает куча людей в том числе
civilians. Where is the logic? I, I say again,
и мирных Где логика я я ещё раз говорю
we are not Az in politics. I, for example, am not Az in
мы в политике не Аз Я например не Аз в
politics.  and our president knows more
политике и президент наш больше знает
how to act, everything on this Uh-huh And
как нужно действовать всё на этом Угу А
who, where did your president come from, his people
кто откуда взялся ваш президент его люди
elect him, or as of course
избирают или как конечно у нас всегда
people always elect him. They elected him, of course,
люди избирают Вот его избирали конечно
yes, everyone elected us, we have a very
да у нас все избирали у нас очень
large number for our president.
большое количество за нашу президенту
how old is he and that's the truth, he's
вот сколько он лет и вот Правда он
always there a little And these
всегда есть там мало И вот эти
coalitions that gather there are nonsense How do you
собираются коалиции там ерунда Как вы
figure out who to vote for How do
разбираетесь за кого проголосовать Как
you know that you need to vote for him
откуда вы знаете что надо за него
And we want a chuchka and a chuchka,
проголосовать А мы хотим чучка а чучка
that is, chue just a chuchka yes that's how it is with the
то есть чуе просто чучка да ва так с
Ukrainian smo  I was in Ukraine
украинский смо это в Украине же был с
watching the TV series there I don’t have any TV I don’t
сериал смотрел там Телевизора нету не
watch
смотрю
God, I’m even telling you about the Ukrainian TV series
Господи я даже про украинский сериал
and you’re not on TV, you’re
тебе говорю а ты не теле вы телевизор
watching TV and
смот а
it’s not there, we’re just on the Internet  We’re sitting and
него нет мы просто в интернете сидим и
watching Zombies, of course, he’s walking and chatting. Yes,
Зомби конечно смотрим он идёт болтает Да
there’s Solovyov’s Skabeeva, look. Of course
там скабееву Соловьёва смотрите Конечно
not, well, I don’t get hung up like that. And so they go, they
нет ну я так не зацикливаюсь А так Идут
go, if Well, yes, I mostly just
Идут если Ну да я ТНТ в основном просто
watch TNT comedy there, all sorts of nonsense,
смотрю там комедийный всякое ерунду есть
you have something. Yes, it glues this so
что-то у вас Да от склеивает такое так
poison is so  No, I don’t look at it, it hurts,
яд такая Нет я не смотрю больно-то это
if you go to your father’s, then you can
если к отцу заехать то там можно что что
go there for a day, if you go he’ll
заехать на день цу если заехать он а
see Yes  Yes, of course, and in your country it is
смот Да скобе его Да конечно и у вас оно
transmitted by airborne droplets. As I
воздушно капельным путём передаётся Я
understand it, yes, that’s why you’re wearing a mask. Yes, you’re
так понял да поэтому вы в маске Да
sitting. No, my father
сидите Нет у меня отец далеко от меня
lives far away from me. This is where, well, 300 km. Yes, it’s in
живёт далеко это где Ну 300 км Да это В
some wilds. Yes, no, not in the wilds.
дебрях каких-то да нет о не В дебрях у
We have a lot of cities, Russia is what it is, I
нас городов то много у нас россия-то
just mean that it’s far away
какая просто имею в виду что далеко
I got it No, there I thought I
Понял Не ну там Думал я-то к мужу
just moved to my husband Yeah I understand Well then he
перебралась просто Ага понял Ну да пото
said Be patient with me Carry me in your arms too  on the
сказал Терпи меня Носи на руках и мне по
drum and you
барабану и вы его
carry it I
носите Я ему
told him to carry me in his arms
сказала меня носить на руках
But damn, no, look, I’m
Та блин не вот смотри я как психиатр
starting to be a psychiatrist. I have a lot of
начинаю У меня много
nerf with you,
нер с вами
yes, yes, I don’t pull it out, but
очень да да я не вытягиваю да у меня
sometimes I’m right. I told me, from me, all
иногда спра Я сказала меня от меня все
Ukrainians switch, change, spread
украинцы переключаются меняются меня
rot on me  [ __ ] you can withstand them how you
гнобить пох выдержишь как ты их
can withstand them trained now you are
выдерживает тренировался вот сейчас вы
such a character you know me at all I don’t know
такой персонаж вы меня ука вообще яж нет
what I did, I’m kind and good And
А что я сделала-то я и добрая хорошая А
what is bad or something I’m not against people, I feel
что плохая что ли Я же не против людей
sorry for everyone  It’s a pity, I’m not a
всех жалко мне всех Жалко я же не
fool, I feel sorry for everyone, I just can’t
дурочка мне всех жалко просто я не могу
diagnose yours, so I
провести диагностику вашу так вот не
can’t make a definitive diagnosis, it’s
могу поставить диагноз окончательно это
tormenting me, I was just going to see a psychologist
меня мучает как раз я к психологу
or a psychiatrist. I don’t know,
собиралась или к психиатру Я не знаю к
go see someone. Yes, I
кому-нибудь сходите Да я думаю
don’t think I can. Well, that’s enough.  Why are you sending me to a
на не могу Ну хватит Почем меня в
mental hospital, not not to a mental hospital,
психушку отправляете не не в психушку
just for
просто на
diagnostics, why can you reveal
диагностику зачем вы может откроете
some deviations to science without
какое-то отклонения так ещё не до
researching yet? What kind of deviations do I have? Well,
исследова Какие у меня отклонения Ну уж
thank you, you’re Russian for having
спасибо Вы уж русских за у меня уж
deviations.  look, that is, it’s not
отклонения Не ну смотрите то есть Э не
every day that you meet a person in a mask and a
каждый день встретишь человека в маске и
cap. You
в пилотке
know, in a jacket, also a jacket. Yes, glasses, yes, that
Понимаете в кофте ещё кофте Да очках да
is. This, and also the glasses that they put in me
то есть Вот это да ещё очки которые мне
in all places, something something is Well, after all,
засунули во все места-то что-то что-то
what  - you
есть Вот ну всё-таки чем-то вы
are showing it, you don’t just
проявляете вот вы не просто так это всё
put it all on like that, that is, there is something sitting inside you
одели так то есть у вас что-то внутри
and this is your inner
сидит и вот это ваша внутре внутренняя
su sitting inside because I don’t want unpleasant ones,
су сидит потому что я не хочу неприятные
these are all Ukrainians now  they also
вот эти вот сейчас все украинцы тоже
take down all the memes and I don’t want to. That’s why I
снимают все мемы и я не хочу Я поэтому
wore this
одела Вот эту вот туку
cap here. Well, my daughter is watching all this nonsense
пилотку Ну да вот эту всю ерунду дочь
because God forbid I don’t want to
потому что смотрит Не дай Бог не хочу
just this nonsense, she just
просто вот эту ерунду она просто с
communicates with Ukrainians very well, she
украинцами общается очень хорошо с
communicates with the girls there. So you’re done
девочками там общается Так вы уже всё
can you show your face at the beginning of the video?
можно в в начале ролика засветили свой
Yes, I
фейс Да я
know you got it now, yes you will, I’ll
знаю ду теперь попали да будете я вам
hit you, damn you, too, you’ll become a meme,
попаду блин вы тоже мемом станете да
yes, let’s do it, but you don’t care, you love it,
давайте а вам-то всё равно вы это любите
yes, let’s do it  we'll exchange a meme like there's
да давайте мы обменяемся мемом типа там
no need to shoot me as a programmer and
не надо меня снимать программист и
a cap like that, or like I'm
пилотка вот так как Зашибись или как я
all Luch cap in will be you know let's call
всех Луч пилотка во будет знаете назовём
m grandfathers
м деды
fought And we haven't forgotten Yes, no, no need to
воевали А мы не забыли Да не не надо на
fight some kind of no, you also need to
воевали какой-то нет вам же надо тоже
somehow  before we forget and you forgot
как-то пока мы не забыли а вы забыли
grandfathers fought granddaughters annealing Yes it will be
деды воевали внучки отжига Да будет Вот
like this Get hurt Are you laughing or something I’ll
так Зашибись Вы что смеётесь что ли е я
definitely never anneal me so
точно не отжига никогда чтоб меня так
it’s you now  You don’t need to beat me,
это сейчас же вы ти Мить строми меня не
you have such a voice, just like
надо у вас такой голос прям как
some kind of combatant,
комбатант какой-то
just like my husband always tells you to go
прям что у меня муж всегда говорит тебе
to school as a teacher, you should have gone to school. Oh, God forbid, don’t,
в школу училкой надо было идти Ой не дай
children, animals, he says he
бог не надо дете звери говорит он так
doesn’t like children that much or something, no, I
детей не любит что ли нет
don’t have children.  I really
Нет я детей очень
like to
люблю
eat no Well, you have something,
кушать нет Ну у вас что-то есть такое
you know, it’s pathological and brutal, it’s a little bit
знаете патологическая зверское немножко
I can’t quite figure it out
я вот не могу до конца разобраться Вот
You’re making jokes So you’re disguising
вы так под под шуточки Так вы маскирует
it as something of your own Here’s something Give me
это какую-то свою вот что-то есть Дай
leave me alone I'm very good I've never
отстаньте Я очень хороший Я никогда в
even hit my child's hand anywhere
жизни своего ребёнка даже ладошки нигде
Wait, how good are you?
не стукнула Подождите как Вы хорошие
If you
Если вы
support the special operation,
поддерживаете спецоперацию
she told me everyone It's a pity for me to
сказала мне всех Жалко я ещё раз мне
tell you again or something You think a maniac
сказать что ли Это думаете маньяку
who kills his victims doesn't feel sorry for him
который убиват своих жертв не жалко Вот
There he killed 20 people for him  it’s a pity and
он там убил 20 человек ему жалко и вот
now you are like this maniac, that is,
вы сейчас вы как этот маньяк так то есть
you support the president, he is people,
вы поддерживаете президента он людей
people, you feel sorry for them, and our president is
людей Вам их жалко е у наш президент уж
certainly not people. He didn’t come and kill
точно не людей Он не пришёл и не прибил
anyone  how well from his decision so from
никого как ну от его решения так от
what his decision there are still 30 commanders there
какого его решения там ещё командиров 30
his decision and his decision he
штук его решение причём его решение он
said to Poti just and tidy up This has to do with his
сказал Поти просто и прибрать Это причём
decision Well, really, this is
его решение Ну правда это глупость
some kind of stupidity, the president told everyone dito
какая-то президент сказал каждому дито
in front of everyone there how many thousands of people
перед всеми там сколько тысяч человек
went to fight and  he came, our president
пошло воевать а он пришёл президент у
tells each person who to
нас указывает каждому человеку да кого
kill, who not
прибить кого не
to kill, they calmed down Yes, I’m all right
прибить успокоились Да я всё о нормально
Yes, they turned off well sometimes, so you know,
Да выключились хорошо иногда так знаете
I advise you Take a
я Вам советую Возьмите
pillow on the wall and attach it with such
подушку на стенку так прибей с такими
things so that  and you’re strangling, yes, and beat him,
штучками чтобы и у душите да и вот бейте
beat him, sometimes you want to. No, you
е бейте иногда вот хочется Да нет вы
just finished off this, they finished off, they finished off
просто вот это вот добили добили добили
the president. Well, he’s alone and there are 000 people
президент Ну он один а там 000 человек
coming, he told everyone who to kill,
идёт он что каждому сказал кого прибить
who not to kill, and where did they get it from
кого не прибить а откуда они получили
if they’re coming at them too?  they’ll
если на них Идут они также
kill you And why did they climb into everything, they could have
прибьют А что они полезли в все могли
surrendered And that’s it And nothing would have happened And that
сдаться И всё И ничего бы не было А что
yours didn’t surrender Why did ours surrender
ваши не сдались А зачем наши сдадутся вы
to us or something, come
к нам что ли
stop, that is, yours came to us and
пошли стоп то есть ваши пришли к нам и
we to stop the war  must give up
мы чтобы остановить войну должны сдаться
yes yes, for
да да
sure this cap is putting a little pressure on your
вам точно эта пилотка немного давит на
brain Well, try this cap Let's
мозг А ну попробуйте вть пилотку Давайте
try without the cap Maybe it's a
попробуем без пилотки Может это
magic cap you take off the cap and a
волшебная пилотка вы снимаете пилотку и
completely different person disappears let's No
совсем другой человек стаёт давайте Нет
I was like that yesterday Let's try
я вчера такая же была Давайте попробуем
take off the cap No you're afraid Yes she is
снимите пилотку Нет вы боитесь Да она у
you Bewitched no no yes
вас Заколдованная нету нет да
Bewitched Pilot everything is fine
Заколдованная Пилот всё нормально Ну
Well, then let’s just take off
ладно давайте тогда просто снимайте
the cap No, I say, let’s
пилотку Нет я говорю давайте тогда
switch then and Are you afraid to talk without the cap?
переключаюсь а Боитесь без пилотки
No, I  I’ll go to others,
поговорить Да нет я пойду другим нерум
no, look, you’re without a cap, I understand, I understood
не вот смотрите вы без пилотки я понял я
how a psychiatrist got to the bottom of your pain, you
как психиатр докопался до вашей боли
know what kind of psychiatrist you’re not a psychiatrist, you’re
знаете какой психиатр вы не психиатр вы
just yourself Koshchei had a problem with an
просто сам У Кощея была там проблема с
egg there, I think you yourself And you have
яйцом Мне кажется вы сами А у вас
a cap, here’s a cap Enchanted, so they
пилотка вот пилотка Заколдованная так
put a cap on you  and you started to
одели на вас пилотку и вы стали типа
take off your cap and but I’m sitting in kindergarten and
снять пилотку и но в детском саду сижу и
talking to a child, honestly, the tray is
с ребнком общаюсь вот честно лотку вот
just what psychologists say, they themselves are a
просто говорят психологи они сами
little crazy If you’re a psychologist Well,
чуть-чуть долбанутые Если Вы психолог Ну
it’s real  this is a hat, this is
вот реально вот это вот шапка вот это
what they put on, this is some kind of nonsense Well,
вот одели вот это вот бред какой-то Ну
this is really a kindergarten Well, with Wait, the
вот реально детский сад Ну с Подождите
children are choosing now switch, I just
дети выбирают сейчас переключись просто
want to say goodbye first Well,
хочу сказать до свидания сперва Ну
say goodbye Take off, you know how they
скажите до свидания Сними знаете как
take off a hat to say goodbye Well,
снимают чтобы до свидания сказать Ну
take off The pilot of the nerve  you there with a swastika
снимите Пилот нерва у вас там с свастика
on me, what is Lesna thinking about,
на у меня что тут Лесна что ли думает
who is thinking about taking them off, well then take them off Let’s talk like that
кто о сняли ну то ж снимите Давайте так
And he wants to take them off and then make
поговори А хочет снять потом сделать
this meme without a cap, like I
этот мем без пилотки меня что типа я
took them off  the cap was humiliated there, Lord,
сняла пилотку унизила там Господи ещё
maybe 20 more
меня может 20
people, yes, you know, one of the most
человек да вы знаете один из наи
interesting characters for non-
интереснейших персонажей для не не
characters of forty-year-old people for
персонажей сорокалетних людей для
research, so let’s say the characters
исследований так вот скажем персонажи А
Why should I be researched, no, no, you’re all
зачем меня исследова не не надо вы все
there, no need to investigate me, I’m
там не надо меня исследовать У меня всё
fine actually No  Well, well, the cap,
нормально на самом Не ну а ну пилотка
there’s something magical in this cap,
что-то в этой пилотке есть магическое
why is this cap ours, it’s
почему это пилотка наша это гордость
our pride and we won’t forget where we got it from.
наша и мы её не сни откуда её взяли
Maybe you know it once, someone was
Может её когда-то знаете на воне кого-то
killed in that cap
в этой пилотке убили
and no, I bought it, I was  I would be proud if I
и нет я купила я была бы горда чтобы я
found such a cap where for someone,
нашла такую пилотку где чтобы кого-то ну
well, from the war from somewhere, well, I don’t have such a
вот с войны откуда-то ну нет такой
cap, yes,
пилотки у
take it off. I don’t have a
меня да снимайте У меня нет у меня есть
metal detector, Nuno, I can’t find non-
металлоискатель нуно я не могу найти не
valuable things from this, well, from the war, I want it
ценные вещи с это ну с войны хочется
too where  - somehow
тоже где-то как-то какой-то медальку
we should even leave some kind of medal at home, we found a lot of
даже дома оставить мы там находили много
things at home, we
вещей дома
left you there,
оставили вас там
plagued, you see, this is the third or
зачумленная видите Вы уже третий раз или
fourth time you say goodbye. This is also
четвёртый Говорите до свидания Это тоже
some kind of pathology. Okay, I’ll move on
какая-то патология Ладно буду отселять
further  Okay Wait a second then
дальше Ладно Подождите секунду тогда
switch
переключите
now something weird is going to happen
раз сейчас что-то стрёмное будет
Lord is he there or something here I can’t
Господи что он там что ли здесь я не
and why didn’t you switch And I’m waiting for what kind of
а вы что не переключились А я жду какой
surprise you are Now
вы сюрприз Сейчас
I’m no surprise I’m not annealing I
отож Я никакой сюрприз не отжига Мне
just need to go on business I had to leave
просто надо по делу сходить было отойти
And  the headphones are right
А наушники же
next to me
рядом
Well, what are you doing already making a meme about
вот Ну и чем вы занимаетесь уже мем про
me not not reading the news but I do
меня делаете не не Новости читаю а а я
n’t
уже не
read it anymore Let’s
читаю Давайте
basically don’t read on telegram I try
в телеграме в принципе не читаю стараюсь
not to
не
read anywhere I don’t read I don’t watch I don’t read
читать нигде не читаю не смотрю не читаю
And with you  my husband has been on the road for a long time
А у вас муж давно в это в
No, not for a long time He’s young,
разъездах Нет не давно Он молодой у
I’m 40 and he’s 30 I mean,
меня мне 40 а ему 30 име в виду неделю
you haven’t seen him for a week in a month, how many
уже вы его не видели месяц сколько чтото
kzi
кзи
No, my husband is 30 years old, I’m
Нет у меня у меня мужу 30 лет У меня всё
fine with this, so don’t
хорошо с этим так что не
worry about it  for
переживайте за
me it’s me that’s old for him and not him for
меня это я для него старая а не он для
me, well, what’s in the news you have
меня ну что там в новостях у вас другие
other news Yes absolutely
же новости Да абсолютно
Yes with us And tell me what what in
Да у нас А скажи что что у вас в
the News in the news they
Новостях в новостях
write like that in short the blogger made a new mm
так пишут короче блогер сделал новый мм
about an aunt with a cap
про тётку с пилоткой
Well  Is it really true, well, it’s no longer necessary Well,
Ну правда что ли уже ну не надо Ну
please, auntie with a cap,
пожалуйста тётка с пилоткой
auntie and
тётка и
cape,
пилотка тётка
auntie cape Well, don’t let us send her to you, my
пилотка Ну пусть у вас нам не надо её
husband
меня муж
will kill me, he’ll say she climbed in, and he
убьёт скажет залезла а это он мне
showed me this, in general, this is the chat
показал вообще это вот чат
roulette
рулетку
Hello Mush on you
Алло Муш на выт
turned off I don’t know what  it was
отключил Я не знаю что це было
In short, you walk like this You walk around, you want to
Короче так ходишь Ходишь хочешь по
put yourself in a pile like this Ale
спилкування ставляться до вй так Але
Koli, you know, people put it on themselves, you
Коли вот знаете люди надягають на себе
can see it’s here  in the attic we don’t call
ло видно щось вот з чердаком не зовсим
that other colleagues licari
так дру колеги ликари
psychologists who else write there write
психологи хто там ще напишить напишить
your
свою
version of what we talked about today Yak
версию того что мы сегодня побачили Як
tse yavishche name Yak description I think the science of
це явище назва Як описа Я думаю наука
such classifications is so that at once
такои класификации так тому что зараз
especially PD hour to the cob of
особливо ПД час початку
special operations axis Tsey phenomenon progress
спецоперации ось Цей феномен прогресу
we need a diagnostician classics and  rozrobiti
нам треба диагност класику и розробити
method jubilant to that scho medicine ma
метод ликування тому що медицина ма
income  nat to such people Slava
доходи нать до таких людей Слава
ukraini write na y Ista
украини пись на й Иста
I don’t know why is this for why are you
Я не знаю для чого це тоб для чого тоб
there to marvel at the ocey face Ale for you
там дивитись на оцей фейс Але для тебе
there is one two or three clicks Aleti trimae
це один два або три клика Але ти тримае
me and I will say in me there A bunch of
мене и я буду казати в мене там Купа
fouls and in me  be cool set up to be
фолов и в мене буде класний настр щоб
robiti but cool video write on th Ista pok
робити но крути видео пись на й Иста пок
Andriy
Андрий
So come on, I'll check for you
Так давай я тея